<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RestaurantCusineApp</string>

    <string name="chineseInfo">Chinese cuisine is an important part of Chinese culture, which includes cuisine originating from the diverse regions of China, as well as from Chinese people in other parts of the world. Because of the Chinese diaspora and historical power of the country, Chinese cuisine has influenced many other cuisines in Asia, with modifications made to cater to local palates.

The preference for seasoning and cooking techniques of Chinese provinces depend on differences in historical background and ethnic groups. Geographic features including mountains, rivers, forests and deserts also have a strong effect on the local available ingredients, considering climate of China varies from tropical in the south to subarctic in the northeast. Imperial, royal and noble preference also plays a role in the change of Chinese cuisines. Because of imperial expansion and trading, ingredients and cooking techniques from other cultures are integrated into Chinese cuisines over time.

The most praised "Four Major Cuisines" are Chuan, Lu, Yue and Huaiyang, representing West, North, South and East China cuisine correspondingly. Modern "Eight Cuisines" of China are Anhui 徽菜 Huīcài, Cantonese 粵菜 Yuècài, Fujian 閩菜 Mǐncài, Hunan 湘菜 Xiāngcài, Jiangsu 蘇菜 Sūcài, Shandong 魯菜 Lǔcài, Sichuan 川菜 Chuāncài, and Zhejiang 浙菜 Zhècài cuisines.

Color, smell and taste are the three traditional aspects used to describe Chinese food,as well as the meaning, appearance and nutrition of the food. Cooking should be appraised from ingredients used, cuttings, cooking time and seasoning.

It is considered inappropriate to use knives on the dining table.Chopsticks are the main eating utensils for Chinese food, which can be used to cut and pick up food.\n</string>
    <string name="mexicanInfo">Mexican cuisine began about 9,000 years ago, when agricultural communities such as the Maya formed, domesticating maize, creating the standard process of corn nixtamalization, and establishing their foodways. Successive waves of other Mesoamerican groups brought with them their own cooking methods. These included the Olmec, Teotihuacanos, Toltec, Huastec, Zapotec, Mixtec, Otomi, Purépecha, Totonac, Mazatec, and Mazahua.

The Mexica establishment of the Aztec Empire created a multi-ethnic society where many different foodways became infused. The staples are native foods, such as corn, beans, squash, amaranth, chia, avocados, tomatoes, tomatillos, cacao, vanilla, agave, turkey, spirulina, sweet potato, cactus, and chili pepper.

After the Spanish conquest of the Aztec Empire in the 16th century, Europeans introduced a number of other foods, the most important of which were meats from domesticated animals (beef, pork, chicken, goat, and sheep), dairy products (especially cheese and milk), and rice. While the Spanish initially tried to impose their own diet on the country, this was not possible.

African and Asian influences were also introduced into the indigenous cuisine during this era as a result of African slavery in New Spain and the Manila-Acapulco Galleons.

Over the centuries, this resulted in regional cuisines based on local conditions, such as those in Oaxaca, Veracruz and the Yucatán Peninsula. Mexican cuisine is an important aspect of the culture, social structure and popular traditions of Mexico. The most important example of this connection is the use of mole for special occasions and holidays, particularly in the South and Center regions of the country. For this reason and others, traditional Mexican cuisine was inscribed in 2010 on the Representative List of the Intangible Cultural Heritage of Humanity by UNESCO.\n</string>
    <string name="thaiInfo">Thai cooking places emphasis on lightly prepared dishes with strong aromatic components and a spicy edge. Thai chef McDang characterises Thai food as demonstrating "intricacy; attention to detail; texture; color; taste; and the use of ingredients with medicinal benefits, as well as good flavor", as well as care being given to the food\'s appearance, smell and context. Australian Thai food critic and enthusiast Lawrence Emanuel observes that unlike many other cuisines, Thai cooking rejects simplicity and is about "…the juggling of disparate elements to create a harmonious finish, particularly in Som Tum Pu Pla Ra".

In 2017, seven Thai dishes appeared on a list of the "World's 50 Best Foods"— a online poll of 35,000 people worldwide by CNN Travel. Thailand had more dishes on the list than any other country. They were: tom yam goong (4th), pad Thai (5th), som tam (6th), massaman curry (10th), green curry (19th), Thai fried rice (24th) and som tum pu pla ra (36th).\n</string>
    <string name="japaneseInfo">Japanese cuisine encompasses the regional and traditional foods of Japan, which have developed through centuries of social and economic changes. The traditional cuisine of Japan (和食 washoku) is based on rice with miso soup and other dishes; there is an emphasis on seasonal ingredients. Side dishes often consist of fish, pickled vegetables, and vegetables cooked in broth. Seafood is common, often grilled, but also served raw as sashimi or in sushi. Seafood and vegetables are also deep-fried in a light batter, as tempura. Apart from rice, staples include noodles, such as soba and udon. Japan also has many simmered dishes such as fish products in broth called oden, or beef in sukiyaki and nikujaga.

Dishes inspired by foreign food—in particular Chinese food like ramen, fried dumplings, and gyōza—as well as foods like spaghetti, curry, and hamburgers have become adopted with variants for Japanese tastes and ingredients. Historically, the Japanese shunned meat, but with the modernization of Japan in the 1880s, meat-based dishes such as tonkatsu and yakiniku have become common. Japanese cuisine, particularly sushi, has become popular throughout the world. In 2011, Japan overtook France in number of Michelin-starred restaurants and has maintained the title since.\n</string>
    <string name="americanInfo">American cuisine reflects the history of the United States of America, blending the culinary contributions of many different groups of people from around the world, including indigenous American Indians, African Americans, Asians, Europeans, Pacific Islanders, and South Americans. Early Native Americans utilized a number of cooking methods in early American Cuisine that have been blended with early European cooking methods to form the basis of American cuisine. The European settlement of the Americas yielded the introduction of a number of various ingredients, spices, herbs, and cooking styles to the latter. The various styles continued expanding well into the 19th and 20th centuries, proportional to the influx of immigrants from many different nations; this influx nurtured a rich diversity in food preparation throughout the country.

When the colonists came to the colonies, they farmed animals for clothing and meat in a similar fashion to what they had done in Europe. They had cuisine similar to their previous British cuisine. The American colonial diet varied depending on the settled region in which someone lived. Commonly hunted game included deer, bear, buffalo, and wild turkey. A number of fats and oils made from animals served to cook much of the colonial foods. Prior to the Revolution, New Englanders consumed large quantities of rum and beer, as maritime trade provided them relatively easy access to the goods needed to produce these items: rum was the distilled spirit of choice, as the main ingredient, molasses, was readily available from trade with the West Indies. In comparison to the northern colonies, the southern colonies were quite diverse in their agricultural diet.

During the 18th and 19th centuries, Americans developed many new foods. During the Progressive Era of the late 19th and early 20th centuries, c. 1890s–1920s, food production and presentation became more industrialized. One characteristic of American cooking is the fusion of multiple ethnic or regional approaches into completely new cooking styles. A wave of celebrity chefs began with Julia Child and Graham Kerr in the 1970s, with many more following after the rise of cable channels, such as the Food Network and Cooking Channel, in the late 20th century.\n</string>

    <string name="chineseRestaurants">China 1 \n Address: 2026 Milledge Ave, Athens, GA 30605 \n Phone: (706) 850-7788 \n\nDonna Chang\'s \n Address: 4741, 1664 S Lumpkin St, Athens, GA 30606 \n Phone: (706) 215-9100 \n\nChef Ming \n Address: 1720 Epps Bridge Pkwy #107, Athens, GA 30606 \n Phone: (706) 552-3233 \n</string>
    <string name="mexicanRestaurants">Tlaloc \n Address: 1225 N Chase St, Athens, GA 30601 \n Phone: (706) 613-9301 \n\nTaqueria La Parilla \n Address: 2439 Jefferson Rd, Athens, GA 30606 \n Phone: (706) 549-4977 \n\nSr. Sol \n Address: 2455 W Broad St, Athens, GA 30606 \n Phone: (706) 850-7112 \n</string>
    <string name="thaiRestaurants">Thai Spoon \n Address: 149 N Lumpkin St, Athens, GA 30601 \n Phone: (706) 548-9222 \n\nE3 Thai Cuisine Restaurant \n Address: 269 E Broad St, Athens, GA 30601 \n Phone: (706) 215-9500 \n\nSiri Thai Cuisine \n Address: 367 Primce Ave #1, Athens, GA 30601 \n Phone: (706) 548-7667 \n</string>
    <string name="japaneseRestaurants">Ru Sans of Athens \n Address: 196 Alps Rd, Athens, GA 30606 \n Phone: (706) 552-0488 \n\nInoko Sushi Express \n Address: 2301 College Station Rd, Athens, GA 30605 \n Phone: (706) 546-5662 \n\nShokitini \n Address: 251 W Clayton St #117, Athens, GA 30601 \n\ Phone: (706) 353-7933 \n</string>
    <string name="americanRestaurants">The World Famous \n Address: 351 N Hull St, Athens, GA 30601 \n Phone: (706) 543-4002 \n\nLast Resort Grill \n Address: 174-184 W Clayton St, Athens, GA 30601 \n Phone: (706) 549-0810 \n\nBrett\'s Casual American \n Address: 3190 Atlanta Hwy #11, Athens, GA 30606 \n Phone: (706) 850-1395 \n</string>

    <string-array name="cuisines">
        <item>Chinese</item>
        <item>Mexican</item>
        <item>Thai</item>
        <item>Japanese</item>
        <item>American</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
